Governor's Efficiency Study Commission SR.397
State Archives of North Carolina
- Working Files, SR.397.3; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
  - Commerce, Department of, 4; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Rural Electrification Authority Research File (folder 2 of 2), undated; 3654; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Rural Electrification Authority Research File (folder 2 of 2))
    - Savings and Loan Division, undated; 3655; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Savings and Loan Division)
    - Summary of Base Budget and Request, 1973-1975; 3656; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Summary of Base Budget and Request)
    - Utilities Commission: Public Utilities Law (Annotated), 1969-1970; 3657; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Utilities Commission: Public Utilities Law (Annotated))
    - Utilities Commission: Public Utilities Law Supplement, 1971; 3658; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Utilities Commission: Public Utilities Law Supplement)
    - Utilities Commission: Reports, 1970-1971; 3659; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Utilities Commission: Reports)
    - Utilities commission: Research Notes, undated; 3660; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Utilities commission: Research Notes)
  - Community Colleges, Department of, 5; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Annual Plan of Work, 1972-1973; 3661; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Annual Plan of Work)
    - Administrative Memoranda (1-0 to 1-15) (folder 1 of 4), 1969-1973; 3662; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Memoranda (1-0 to 1-15) (folder 1 of 4))
    - Administrative Memoranda (2-1 to 3-2) (folder 2 of 4), 1970-1972; 3663; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Memoranda (2-1 to 3-2) (folder 2 of 4))
    - Administrative Memoranda (4-1 to 6-5) (folder 3 of 4), 1968-1972; 3664; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Memoranda (4-1 to 6-5) (folder 3 of 4))
    - Administrative Memoranda (7-1 to 16-3) (folder 4 of 4), 1968-1972; 3665; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administrative Memoranda (7-1 to 16-3) (folder 4 of 4))
    - Continuing Education Programs, 1973; 3666; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Continuing Education Programs)
    - Degree and Diploma Programs, 1973; 3667; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Degree and Diploma Programs)
    - Information and Publication, 1973; 3668; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Information and Publication)
    - Intra-Office Procedures, 1972; 3669; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Intra-Office Procedures)
    - Lists and Charts, 1972; 3670; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Lists and Charts)
    - Planning and Coordination, 1972-1973; 3671; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Planning and Coordination)
    - Planning for the North Carolina Community College System (Vol. 1-4), 1970; 3672; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Planning for the North Carolina Community College System (Vol. 1-4))
    - Position Management Classification and Organization, 1971-1972; 3673; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Position Management Classification and Organization)
    - Publications (folder 1 of 2), 1963-1973; 3674; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Publications (folder 1 of 2))
    - Publications (folder 2 of 2), 1971-1973; 3675; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Publications (folder 2 of 2))
    - Personnel Lists, 1973; 3676; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Personnel Lists)
    - Student Personnel and Program Resources, 1973; 3677; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Student Personnel and Program Resources)
  - Governor's Office, 6; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Implementation Progress Report, 1974; 3678; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Progress Report)
    - Introduction, 1973; 3679; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Introduction)
    - Memorandums, 1973; 3680; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Memorandums)
    - Recommendations: Implemented, 1974; 3681; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented)
    - Recommendations: In Progress, 1974; 3682; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: In Progress)
    - Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1974; 3683; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Unacceptable)
    - Research File, undated; 3684; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Research File)
  - Human Resources, Department of, 7; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Administration: Implementation Progress Reports, 1973-1975; 3685; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administration: Implementation Prog)
    - Administration: Introduction and Other Recommendations, 1973; 3686; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administration: Introduction and Ot)
    - Administration Recommendations: Implemented (folder 1 of 2), 1973-1974; 3687; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administration Recommendations: Imp)
    - Administration Recommendations: Implemented (folder 2 of 2), 1973-1974; 3688; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administration Recommendations: Imp)
    - Administration Recommendations: In Process, 1973-1975; 3689; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administration Recommendations: In)
    - Administration Recommendations: More Study, 1973-1974; 3690; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administration Recommendations: Mor)
    - Administration Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1973; 3691; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administration Recommendations: Una)
    - Administration: Reorganization Recommendations Back-up Data, 1973; 3692; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administration: Reorganization Reco)
    - Administration: Session Bill, 1973; 3693; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Administration: Session Bill)
    - Commission for the Blind: Accounting and Management File, undated; 3694; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Accountin)
    - Commission for the Blind: Administrative and Introduction Materials, 1973; 3695; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Administr)
    - Commission for the Blind: Base Budget Request, 1972-1973; 3696; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Base Budg)
    - Commission for the Blind: Business Enterprises, undated; 3697; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Business)
    - Commission for the Blind: Governor Morehead School Budget Report Review, undated; 3698; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Governor)
    - Commission for the Blind: Governor Morehead School Laundry Data, 1972; 3699; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Governor)
    - Commission for the Blind: Governor Morehead School Monthly Budget Report, 1973; 3700; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Governor)
    - Commission for the Blind: Governor Morehead School Personnel Descriptions, 1973-1974; 3701; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Governor)
    - Commission for the Blind: Governor Morehead School Recommendation Report, 1973; 3702; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Governor)
    - Commission for the Blind: Medical Program, undated; 3703; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Medical P)
    - Commission for the Blind: Organizational Charts, 1972; 3704; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Organizat)
    - Commission for the Blind: Recommendation Reports, 1973; 3705; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Recommend)
    - Commission for the Blind: Rehabilitation Division Research File, 1973; 3706; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Rehabilit)
    - Commission for the Blind: Social Services Division, 1970-1973; 3707; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Commission for the Blind: Social Se)
    - Health Services: Administrative and General Data, and Review Notes (folder 1 of 2), 1970-1975; 3708; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Administrative and)
    - Health Services: Administrative and General Data, and Review Notes (folder 2 of 2), 1970-1975; 3709; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Administrative and)
    - Health Services: Epidemiology Division Research Materials, 1973; 3710; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Epidemiology Divis)
    - Health Services: Laboratory Division Publications, 1972-1973; 3711; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Laboratory Divisio)
    - Health Services: Medical Examiner System Publications, 1973; 3712; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Medical Examiner S)
    - Health Services: Medicaid Standard System Involving Nursing Homes, 1973; 3713; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Medicaid Standard)
    - Health Services: Notes on Cost and Positions, undated; 3714; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Notes on Cost and)
    - Health Services: Organizational Realignment, 1974; 3715; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Organizational Rea)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 1, Charge Cost Fee for Bacteriological Surveillance of Public Water Supplies, 1973; 3716; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 1,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 10, Billing Units to Budget and Accounting, 1973; 3717; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 10,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 11, Eliminate Syphilis Serology Before Marrying, 1973; 3718; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 11,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 12, Abolish Positions Vacant Six Months, 1973; 3719; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 12,)
    - Health Services: Reccomendation 13, Consider All Budget Change Requests, 1973; 3720; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Health Services: Recommendation 14, Let State Health Director Make Budget, 1973; 3721; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 14,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 15, Make Regional Office Organizational Decision, 1973; 3722; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 15,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 16, Stop Typing Expense Account Form, 1973; 3723; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 16,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 17, Study Feasibility of Central Vital Records, 1973; 3724; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 17,)
    - Health Records Recommendation 18, Develop Information System Plan (folder 1 of 2), 1972-1973; 3725; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Records Recommendation 18, D)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 18, Develop Information System Plan (folder 2 of 2), 1972-1973; 3726; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 18,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 19, Automate Vital Records Certificates (folder 1 of 2), 1973; 3727; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 19,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 19, Automate Vital Records Certificates (folder 2 of 2), 1973; 3728; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 19,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 20, Let Training Perform Management Development, 1973; 3729; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 20,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 21, Make Training a Budget Line Item, 1973; 3730; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 21,)
    - Health Services: Recommendation 22, Study State Clearinghouse Mechanism, 1973; 3731; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Recommendation 22,)
    - Health Services: Sanitary Engineering Board Publications, 1971-1973; 3732; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Health Services: Sanitary Engineeri)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Black Mountain Alcoholic Rehabilitation Center, 1972-1973; 3733; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Black M)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Broughton Hospital, 1971-1973; 3734; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Brought)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Caswell Center, 1971-1973; 3735; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Caswell)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Caswell Center Master Plan, 1972; 3736; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Caswell)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Canteen Operations, 1971-1973; 3737; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Canteen)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Cherry Hospital, 1973; 3738; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Cherry)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Dorothea Dix Hospital, 1971-1973; 3739; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Dorothe)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Employee Cafeteria, 1958, 1971-1973; 3740; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Employe)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: John Umstead Hospital, 1969-1974; 3741; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: John Um)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Murdoch Center, 1973; 3742; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Murdoch)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: North Carolina Institution Farms, 1971-1973; 3743; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: North C)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: O'Berry Center, 1972-1973; 3744; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: O')
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Pharmacy, 1973; 3745; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Pharmac)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Sanatorium System General File, undated; 3746; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Sanator)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Sanatorium System Recommendation 1, Close Western North Carolina Sanatorium, 1971-1973; 3747; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Sanator)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Sanatorium Recommendation 2, Sell Seven Western Employee Houses, 1973; 3748; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Sanator)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Sanatorium Recommendation 4, Project Cost Figures for FGEs, 1969-1973; 3749; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Sanator)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Sanatorium Recommendation 5, Double Employee Meal Charge at Cafeteria, 1973; 3750; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Sanator)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Sanatorium Recommendation 6, Double Rent for State Owned Housing, 1973; 3751; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Sanator)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Sanatorium Recommendation 7, Abolish Fourteen Dietary Positions, 1973; 3752; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Sanator)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Sanatorium Recommendation 8, Abolish Ten Housekeeping Positions, 1973; 3753; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Sanator)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Sewing Room, 1972; 3754; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Sewing)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Schools for the Deaf, 1973; 3755; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Schools)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Walter B. Jones Alcoholic Rehabilitation Center, 1971-1973; 3756; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Walter)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Western Carolina Center Accounting Office, 1971-1975; 3757; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Western)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Western Carolina Purchasing Office, 1973; 3758; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Western)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Western Carolina Service Unit, 1972; 3759; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Western)
    - Hospitals and Institutions: Wright School, 1972-1973; 3760; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Hospitals and Institutions: Wright)
    - Medical Services (folder 1 of 2), 1972-1973; 3761; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Medical Services (folder 1 of 2))
    - Medical Services (folder 2 of 2), 1972-1973; 3762; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Medical Services (folder 2 of 2))
    - Medical Services: Hospital Care, 1973; 3763; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Medical Services: Hospital Care)
    - Medical Services: Levels of Care, 1970-1973; 3764; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Medical Services: Levels of Care)
    - Medical Services: Medical Payments to Providers Audit, 1973; 3765; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Medical Services: Medical Payments)
    - Medical Services: National Guard, 1972-1973; 3766; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Medical Services: National Guard)
    - Mental Health: Administrative File, 1972-1973; 3767; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Mental Health: Administrative File)
    - Mental Health: Management Analysis Staff (folder 1 of 2), 1969-1973; 3768; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Mental Health: Management Analysis)
    - Mental Health: Management Analysis Staff (folder 2 of 2), 1969-1973; 3769; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Mental Health: Management Analysis)
    - Mental Health: Services, 1973; 3770; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Mental Health: Services)
    - Reimbursements, 1973; 3771; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Reimbursements)
    - Rental Housing, 1969-1973; 3772; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Rental Housing)
    - Social Services: Administrative Central File, 1973; 3773; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Administrative Cen)
    - Social Services: Administrative Research File, 1970; 3774; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Administrative Res)
    - Social Services: Basic Functions, 1972-1973; 3775; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Basic Functions)
    - Social Services: Co-insurance, 1972-1973; 3776; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Co-insurance)
    - Social Services: Comptroller File (folder 1 of 2), 1972-1973; 3777; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Comptroller File ()
    - Social Services: Comptroller File (folder 2 of 2), 1972-1973; 3778; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Comptroller File ()
    - Social Services: Cost Improvement Program, 1973; 3779; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Cost Improvement P)
    - Social Services: County Social Service Organization, undated; 3780; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: County Social Serv)
    - Social Services: Disability Determination, 1970-1973; 3781; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Disability Determi)
    - Social Services: Economic Opportunity Division Research Files, 1970-1973; 3782; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Economic Opportuni)
    - Social Services: General Statutes, 1971; 3783; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: General Statutes)
    - Social Services: Field Services Division, 1971-1973; 3784; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Field Services Div)
    - Social Services: Flat Grant Payment System, 1972-1973; 3785; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Flat Grant Payment)
    - Social Services: Paternity Support, 1973; 3786; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Paternity Support)
    - Social Services: Psychology Services, 1972; 3787; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Psychology Service)
    - Social Services: Recommendations, 1973; 3788; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Recommendations)
    - Social Services: Removal of Medicaid Providers, 1973; 3789; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Removal of Medicai)
    - Social Services: Solicitation and Line Recommendations, 1973; 3790; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Solicitation and L)
    - Social Services: Welfare Program Divisions, 1970-1973; 3791; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Welfare Program Di)
    - Social Services: Welfare Program Food Stamps, 1973; 3792; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Social Services: Welfare Program Fo)
    - Special Services, 1972-1973; 3793; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Special Services)
    - Statistics and Program Analysis, 1971-1973; 3794; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Statistics and Program Analysis)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation, 1973; 3795; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Vocational Rehabilitation)
    - Word Processing, 1973; 3796; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Word Processing)
  - Justice, Department of, 8; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - General Information, 1972-1973; 3797; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder General Information)
  - Labor, Department of, 9; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Introduction, 1973, 1976; 3798; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Introduction)
    - Monthly Progress Report, 1974; 3799; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Monthly Progress Report)
    - Recommendations: Implemented, 1973; 3800; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented)
    - Recommendations: In Process, 1974; 3801; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: In Process)
    - Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1974; 3802; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Unacceptable)
  - Lieutenant Governor, Office of, 10; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Lieutenant Governor's Office, 1973-1974; 3803; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Lieutenant Governor's Office)
  - Military and Veteran's Affairs, Department of, 11; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.